It seems today
that all you see
Is violence in movies
and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy!
Good evening. I'm Tom Tucker.
The hot new reality
dating show Sex Farm
is coming to Quahog.
Contestants conceal
their identities
by dressing as farm animals
in hopes of finding love.
Auditions are being held
all week
at the long-empty
Miramax offices downtown.
Imagine naming a company
after your mother
and then molesting
everyone who comes in.
Auditions?
Maybe I could meet my person.
Your "person"?
Oh, is your "person"
a good "human"?
You gonna post
your engagement ring with,
"So, this just happened"?
You gonna hashtag #VanLife?
You gonna get murdered
in Florida?
No one's gonna look for you,
you basic white bitch.
This is gonna be awesome.
-I'm gonna try out.
-Well, good luck.
I hope your reality show
goes better than mine did.
This season on Alone,
12 contestants will be droppd
in the wilderness.
Remember, you're on camera,
so don't masturbate.
Remember, you're
on camera, so don't masturbate.
Remember, you're on camera,
so don't masturbate.
I didn't even make it
to the ground.
Thank you
for coming in today, Meg.
We're excited to see
if you have what it takes
to be on Sex Farm.
Thanks. So, is there anything
I need to do for this audition?
No. Most of modern auditions
is just us going through
all your old tweets
to see if there are any racist
or homophobic slurs.
Now, I see you've never
retweeted Bowen Yang. Why?
I see that I was wrong,
and I now understand
comedy is mostly about
getting angry at funny things.
You're in.
This season on Sex Farm,
we're in Quahog, Rhode Island,
with an all-new cast
of horny livestock.
What's going on, guys?
It's me, Corey,
from Corey's World.
After being virally ambushed
while screaming
at my stepmom in a Walmart,
I've taken a demotion from
YouTube to network television.
And I am totally
less-profitably stoked
to be your host tonight
on Sex Farm.
Let's get to know
these filthy animals.
No middle-aged spinster here,
I'm just a frisky
little pussycat.
I'm here
because sleeping in a barn
is preferable
to an unfurled wrestling mat.
I'm ready to swine and dine.
Oink, oink, boink, boink.
Yuck. The herd will decide
who stays
to continue their journey
for love
and who gets put out to pasture.
All part of the barn dance
here on Sex Farm,
where our pronouns
are "yee" and "haw."
I-I don't get that.
Hey, there. Nice ass.
I'm wondering if you're down
for some porkin'.
Oh, my, that's going
right at it, isn't it?
Sorry, little piggy,
I think you's is sloppin'
at the wrong trough.
Oh, uh, sorry.
Uh, hey, there. Nice ass.
I'm wondering if you're down
for some porkin'.
I had to take 80 milligrams
of Thorazine 'cause I'm having
a claustrophobic freak-out
in here.
So, pass.
Wow, you really
packed that away in a hurry.
Thanks.
I may be dressed like a pig,
but I have two stomachs
like a cow.
You're funny.
It's not really a joke.
I'm not expected
to live past 40.
Looks like I made it
just under the wire.
I'm only 18.
Oh, your Liberty
Mutual tote bag threw me off.
It's how I carry my loose fruit.
I like you.
You don't try very hard.
Oh, I'm trying very hard.
What's going on, guys?
It's your boy Corey.
Be sure to check me out
on Cameo.
The producers said
I couldn't mention it,
but I'm betting
they don't even watch the show.
So, a big part of finding love
on the farm
is having our contestants
go on dates
and then be surprised
by a musical act
you've never heard of.
I couldn't believe it.
We walked around the corner,
and there was Barton James.
Won't you hold my hand...
- Oh, my God.
- I love this song.
Make me understand...
Barton James and a girl
in a pig mask?
Yeah, it was a pretty good day.
Man.
Check it out, guys,
Barton James'
new album Country Girl
is now available
exclusively on Deezer.
We had to say that
or he wouldn't show up.
Devout Christian
Barton James was unvaccinated
and a general
pain in the ass to deal with.
What's going on, guys?
Dates have ended,
and it's almost time
to find out who's got the heat
and who's being turned
into meat.
Fan favorite The Cow
is recovering nicely
from his panic attack
at Group Coop.
I don't really care
if I fall in love.
I just need to be done
with this show,
like, as soon as possible.
I haven't taken
a normal breath in...
...three days.
Guys, if you or someone you know
is struggling
with anxiety or depression,
go to SexFarm-BummedOut.com.
Wild cards Pig and Chicken
really hit it off
at the group feces bath.
Let's see if their
connection continues
on their mandatory
reality-show helicopter ride.
I really like
spending time with you.
You're so spontaneous.
I really like you, too.
And I'm sorry for that fart
you're gonna smell.
I knew you wouldn't hear it,
but I didn't think it was
gonna be as bad as it was.
I actually did hear it.
And I think I might be
falling in love with you.
Hey, guys,
what was the one rule I had?
No farting in the helicopter.
I killed bin Laden,
now I'm doing this.
Before we find out
which couple will be the first
put out to pasture,
we're gonna put up a QR code
that's a direct link to Deezer,
where you can hear Barton James
duet with Kyle Rittenhouse.
And the first eliminated
couple is...
...Pig and Chicken.
Which means fan favorite Cow
remains on the farm.
I told producer Josh
I desperately want to go home.
Pig and Chicken,
turn in your hay
and head to the slaughterhouse.
Hey, I'm sorry
I dragged you down.
And I'm sorry I embarrassed you
in front of Bethenny Frankel.
That was Bethenny Frankel?
I thought it was a scarecrow.
Well, the crows were scared.
- Is she gone?
- I-I don't know.
I-I mean, I want the corn,
but I don't want to have to hear
about how much trouble
she's having dating.
Well, I guess this is it.
It was nice while it lasted.
Wait, Pig!
- Yes?
- I don't even know your name.
I'm Meg.
I'm just worried
you won't be as attracted to me
when I take this off.
You're dressed like a pig.
I'll take my chances.
I was right.
You are prettier than a pig.
Your turn.
And I don't care what
you look like under that mask.
That's good, because...
I'm a chicken.
My name is Nugget.
Wait a minute,
you're not related
to the giant chicken, are you?
He's my dad.
-What is it, Peter?
-I forgot to go to college.
Oh, Meg, there you are.
Sit down.
We're watching Sex Farm.
-Have you seen it?
-Mom, I was on it.
-I was the pig.
-What?
Yeah, I don't remember that,
either, but check it out:
the cow escaped and then
a fan vote brought him back.
They caught him hiding on one
of those Chick-fil-A billboards.
Once again,
please stop voting for me.
This is a cry for help.
I swear to God, I'll jump.
That guy is so funny.
I'm gonna vote for him
a hundred times.
Well, have fun.
Where are you going
all dolled up?
What? Oh, that is not
offensive to dolls.
Stop trying
to make yourself angry.
-I have a date.
-With who?
Um, nobody you know.
See you later.
She's dating again?
Whatever happened to that
illusionist she was seeing?
I never left, Peter.
Wow. Wait,
why are you still here?
Well, I'm an illusionist,
so I'm either homeless
or I have a $100 million
residency in Las Vegas.
Oh, my God,
the cow is really gonna jump.
You made me do this.
This is on you, producer Josh.
I'm all right.
I landed just so.
It's so cool learning
about your world.
So, okay, tell me this:
is Colonel Sanders
like your Adolf Hitler?
No, the colonel
is an honest man.
Our Adolf Hitler
is Kenny Rogers,
with his stupid
Kenny Rogers Roasters.
Kenny Rogers? The gambler?
No, not the gambler.
He was the narrator
who met up with the gambler,
and then shared things
he had learned from the gambler
but at no point was the gambler.
Well, all I know is that
he looked like he was 40
from the time he was 20
until the time he was 90.
And died unable
to close his eyes, yes.
Now, how about that picnic?
When a girl loves a chicken
Can't keep her mind
on nothing else
She'd trade the world
For the good thing
she's found
When a girl loves a chicken
I know exactly how
She feels.
That was the best night's sleep
I've had in ages.
I love you, Meg,
and not just because
you have "egg" in your name.
I love you, too, Nugget.
I want to keep seeing you,
but what if our dads find out?
I guess we'll have to
live a lie, like George Santos.
Hi, I'm gay-straight
Jewish Nazi George Santos,
and I approve this message.
Which is to say it's the worst
thing that's happened to me
since I died on 9/11.
Good morning night.
This was written 18 months ago.
New lies not included.
Nugget? What are you doing here?
I was in the neighborhood
and thought we could
Netflix and chill
or Peacock and.
Peacock: somehow we
don't have Seinfeld or Friends,
and we can't show you
The Cosby Show.
Hey, Meg, can you give me a hand
clasping these Mr. T medallions?
I have an event.
Who's your fine-feathered
friend?
Dad, this is
my boyfriend Nugget.
His father is the giant chicken.
That's it, young lady--
no Peacock for a month.
No Peacock?
But where will I watch
The Croods?
That's not my problem.
Peacock: I don't think we hae
The West Wing either.
Of all the chickens
Meg could have chosen,
she had to choose that one.
Oh, Peter,
you got to back off.
My father never stopped
berating me
when I was dating you,
so as an act of defiance
I married you
just to spite him.
That seems irrelevant.
I don't know, Lois,
it feels like
I've lost my daughter.
Which means I have two sons.
If I'm lucky,
they'll join the army,
and I'll be notified
that they both died
on the same day.
Your two sons died
getting their heads shaved
at orientation.
They didn't even make it
to the barracks.
Oh, the cost of freedom!
Here's a flag
we didn't bother to fold.
I really want to thank you
for inviting me to dinner,
Mr. and Mrs. Griffin.
Hey, Nugget, you ever seen
that video of Fabio
getting hit in the face
by a goose?
-It's hilarious.
-Not for the goose.
-She was killed.
-Oh, then that's doubly funny.
Fabio's got a bloody nose
and a bird is dead.
Mr. Griffin,
that goose had a name.
It was Evelyn.
And she had 23 children.
Here, let me show you
her GoFundMe page.
What's your guys'
Wi-Fi password?
It's "ChickensAreScum,"
and then 22 exclamation points.
It's on the bulletin board
for when we Airbnb the house.
Peter, we are not
Airbnb-ing the house.
Eh, it might be too late
for that.
Hey, is there any soap
in the upstairs bathroom?
If you read the PDF, it said
you had to bring your own soap.
Well, I'll just
use the shampoo as soap.
He's a medical student.
You know, you guys are being
very rude to my boyfriend.
-I love him.
-I've had enough.
Meg, I'm giving you
an old tomato.
And a final demand
or statement of terms,
the rejection of which
will result in retaliation
or a permanent cessation
of relations.
You either break up with him
or you break up with me.
You can't date us both.
Dad, you and I aren't dating.
Oh, so you've made
your choice, then.
Well, I'd like my tomato back.
I'll pack my bags.
What bags?
She literally owns nothing.
Guys, before I go,
I have one thing to say.
Is this a "pause The Last of Us"
type of conversation
or can I "uh-huh"
my way through this?
Peter, turn it off.
If you don't accept Nugget,
you don't accept me.
I'm moving in with him.
You know what the British
are gonna call this?
Megxit.
They're a clever little island.
Meg, please don't go.
You're my only daughter
and I can't imagine
living without you.
Plus, I need your vote
to keep a Billy Bass
-out of our living room.
-I'm sorry, Mom.
My decision has been made.
Goodbye.
Well, now seems like
a good time
to reopen the Billy Bass vote.
All in favor, say aye.
-Aye.
-All opposed?
-Nay.
-Present.
-Coward.
Billy Bass approved.
Billy, what do you think
Meg's gonna say
to the Uber driver?
Take me to the river
Drop me in the water.
Ah, we are thriving
without Meg.
Is something wrong, Peter?
You've barely touched our food.
I heard from Bonnie that
Meg moved out of the house
and Lois could never breastfeed.
What? How'd you hear that?
Oh, Bonnie subscribes
to a service
that alerts her any time
another mom fails.
-That's wild.
-I know.
Donna gives Cleveland Jr.
unlimited
video game time, but...
Peter, isn't it weird
with Meg out of the house?
Nah, it's fine.
Although we got a lot more mice
-around the house now.
-Mice?
Yeah, Meg handled
all our rodent problems.
She used to just squeeze 'em
and pop their heads off.
All except one
that she'd leave alive
to run and go tell the story
to the others.
Meg's a nice girl.
Yeah, when I remodeled my house,
Meg hauled away
all the discarded insulation.
Don't know what she did with it.
Oh, yeah, Meg's great.
She sold me a ton
of insulation super cheap.
Oh, my God, you guys are right.
This one time,
Meg fell down the stairs
a-and she...
and-and she broke her clavicle.
You guys, I think I miss Meg.
Wa-Was there gonna be more
to the story about the stairs?
What do you say we go
to the giant chicken's house
and get my daughter back?
-I'm in.
-Let's do it.
So the laughing was 'cause
your daughter hurt herself?
Honey, did you order
a fat bag of crap?
Stand aside. I'm here
to get my daughter back.
She's not coming with you.
-She's perfectly happy here.
-Are you sure?
We can make this
worth your while.
We're prepared to trade
Brittney Griner.
Hey, stop trading me.
I just want to play basketball.
And smoke weed, apparently.
I wasn't smoking it,
I was just carrying it.
Whatever. I'm still mad
we traded for you
instead of that other guy,
whose name
I had never heard of
and can no longer remember.
Yeah, that poor guy.
Bring him home,
whatever his name is.
Dad, what are you doing here?
Meg, this nonsense has to stop.
You're a Griffin, and...
it's time to, uh... Do...
do your neighbors
always have that bounce house
or is this--
is it a special occasion?
-I really don't know.
-Okay, yeah, but Meg,
I mean it.
We all miss you, and--
Oh, a heavy lady's
rolling into it.
Probably the aunt
who likes to have fun.
Wow, her face got red quick.
Dad, I told you,
Nugget and his family
treat me better
than you guys ever did.
And I won't be coming home.
Dad?
It's a Iron Man house!
Okay, you know what,
I think we need to regroup here.
We're sorry
to have bothered you.
I squashed a boy.
Oh, come on, cheer up, Peter.
Look, the best thing to do
to put all this
Meg drama behind us
is a fun family activity
that we can all do together.
You know, I was supposed
to be here today anyway,
but then Tyler
cancelled his birthday party.
Ice cream sundae bar
with Haribo brand gummi bears?
Tyler! Tyler! Tyler!
Hey, Ty. Guess we got
our wires crossed, huh?
I-It was a numbers thing.
I think his parents made him
invite the T-ball kids.
- All right, Dad! Yeah!
- Good job, Giant Chicken!
Yes!
I've lost my daughter.
Come on, gang.
Group selfie for the family
Instagram account.
Everybody say "seeds."
Seeds!
Griffin? What do you want?
Um, I, uh...
Meg, do you have
a flat dollar bill
for the change machine?
I wanted to play the arcades.
-We don't play the arcades.
-Nerds.
Because we have stand-up games
-in our basement rec room.
-Aw.
Guess you'll just
have to make do
with your crinkled ones.
Honey, the scattered grain
is delicious.
-You outdid yourself.
-Well, don't thank me.
Thank the good people
at Monsanto,
who make delicious grain
that's packed with
antidepressants and steroids.
I'm so glad you decided
to come live with us, Meg.
Me too.
But I couldn't help feel
a little sorry for my dad
at the bowling alley.
He bowled
with the lane guards up.
Without the jeopardy
of a gutter ball,
what is bowling?
He just has his own way
of doing things.
-Yeah, the wrong way.
-Honey...
No, she knows.
That's why she left.
No. I left
because I love your son,
not because I hate my dad.
Meg, either you hate your dad
or you leave this house.
An old tomato.
You're just like him.
What did you say?
You're just... like... him.
Wait, I-I can't hit you.
You're a girl.
Oh, Meg, I'm so happy
you realized
your place is here at home
with your father.
It really wasn't that.
It's just...
all my stuff is here.
What stuff?!
Also, turns out Nugget's gay.
I saw his texts
and it's all tiny cocks.
Oh, "Nugget" Nugget?